<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musical structure app</string>

    <!--Main Activity title-->
    <string name="music_library">Music Library</string>

    <!--Category strings-->
    <string name="playlist_category">Playlists</string>
    <string name="artists_category">Artists</string>
    <string name="albums_category">Albums</string>
    <string name="songs_category">Songs</string>

    <!--Button strings-->
    <string name="back_btn">Back</string>
    <string name="play_btn">Play</string>

    <!--CardView content strings-->
    <string name="playlist_title">Playlist Title</string>
    <string name="album_title">Album title</string>
    <string name="artist_title">Artist title</string>
    <string name="song_title">Song title</string>

    <!--Playlists strings-->
    <string name="playlist_purpose">This activity will show CardViews with all the playlists that the user has</string>
    <string name="playlist_hurdles">The image from the CardView consists of more smaller images from the artists in that playlists.\nAn algorithm that searches the internet for the artist\'s pictures in a certain size would have to be implemented.\nThe number of CardViews per row will have to be responsive to the screen of the device or the portrait/landscape mode. \nIf you press on the CardView then the SongActivity will start with all the songs from that playlist. </string>

    <!--Artists strings-->
    <string name="artist_purpose">This activity will show CardViews with all the artists from the songs</string>
    <string name="artist_hurdles">An algorithm that searches the internet for the artist\'s pictures in a certain size would have to be implemented.\nThe number of CardViews per row will have to be responsive to the screen of the device or the portrait/landscape mode.\nIf you press on the CardView, then the SongActivity will start with all the songs from that artist.</string>

    <!--Albums strings-->
    <string name="album_purpose">This activity will show CardViews with all the albums from the songs</string>
    <string name="album_hurdle">An algorithm that searches the internet for pictures of the albums in a certain size would have to be implemented.\nThe number of CardViews per row will have to be responsive to the screen of the device or the portrait/landscape mode. \nIf you press on the CardView, then the SongActivity will start with all the songs from that album.</string>

    <!--Songs strings-->
    <string name="song_purpose">This activity will show a list with all the songs that the user has. It has also a search song bar. </string>
    <string name="song_hurdles">A search song algorithm would have to be written, in order to search for songs in the users library. Also, when the user will press play on a song in the list, then a media player with now playing will appear. </string>

</resources>
